Here I am, very well, we were
[Music] we
are studying a hen, his name
is Ariel, sometimes he is only known as
the area, he is the most famous area in the
history of Buddhism, he
lived in the year 280 AD,
about 800 years ago. I think that for
Tania Lee, the flood, he, from the author
of the Yoga Sutras, his tradition around
the times, because many of the themes
that Tangier spoke about are found in the
time of the hen,
only after the Christian era, about
200 years later. And I think there may be
some connection with the arrival of
Christianity. The disciple Thomas,
who was a student of Jesus, came to India, to
a place called Tit,
and worked for a king whom the Greeks
called Son of Forest, the Romans
called him Gaspar, and he was one of the three
kings who went to Bethlehem. And Thomas
worked for him, and that was part of
India at that time, now it is part of
Afghanistan. So I think there is a
connection. Thomas, yes, Thomas ended up in
southern India in Madras, which is now
called Chennai.
And he spent a lot of time there, his church is
still there, and he was killed there.
And all of South India is Christian,
Kerala, the state of Kerala, and all those
states. And Nagarjuna comes from those
states, he
comes from the South. And if it's a more
birthplace, and if you go to the monastery, it will be
Meis,
the biggest monastery.
From Bangalore airport, you pass through the
village of the chickens. That's where you
buy coconuts. So if you go with the
coconuts, you stand
at the age of South India.
[Music] He
is the greatest teacher about
emptiness, and this is his greatest book
about emptiness called Wisdom.
And he wrote like 10 or 15 books.
I'm teaching some of them in
Guangzhou, all of his great letters
to kings, to rulers.
And we are learning in Guangzhou
on Viviana's program. If you are
interested, talk to her. It's an
amazing program called The Way of
Kings.
[Music]
And we will be studying Wisdom, which,
his greatest book, became
the basis of all
future explanations of emptiness, so in
any country  In China, Vietnam, Korea,
India, PTI, see anywhere that
studies of emptiness you are studying, you are
studying his works, and I thought it would be
amazing to break it down, spread it out over
5 years, we're going to do it once a
year for 10 years, and we're going to
review wisdom.
There are 3 commentaries that I would like to use.
One is by Jett, they are layers, and it
is probably the best commentary
about the hen,
and it is called The Ocean of Emptiness. PP,
which to the PSOE,
that rich network means proof of
emptiness.
If I like to call the book a
short name, The Ocean of
Emptiness, if we translate it differently,
2,500 pages, it's going to be a
big book. If we translate it as carp, it's
difficult. There is no other master
named Jon and Hamas,
and his dates are
1006,657,748. He wrote a very
digestible book. It's difficult, but it doesn't give you
indigestion or diarrhea.
It's just difficult, but it's not impossible.
So if you read the first 8,000 pages, which
is around 6,000 pages, the
translation
that can be done with our
mixing team  We make about four
thousand leaves a year from walnuts, so we can
do it if we have time. If we do
n't, we have to spend time
fundraising.
If someone else raises
money to finish the
monastery roads, I can't even do magic.
I can do both, and really, we can't do
both. I
raised money because we need
roads here. I can translate that no one
else can do. Do you understand? So help
me.
Don't make me ask. Just do the
studies.
Seven thousand dollars. Ask and talk to
Rob Singer.
Even the new ones have holes. The
new roads are hard work. It's
a big job, but this place is going to
be so amazing if we
finish the roads. If we don't have
two roads,
I'm scared about that road that
goes up
and isn't covered, so
the rain is making the
road smaller and smaller.
I'm scared someone will go flying off
the mountain in a car. So help
me. We have to see how we do it. If
you decide to do something, you can do it,
especially with many countries. And we can do it. It's not
impossible. Don't say
anything like, "I can't," but we did this
building. We did the other one. That
building was two million dollars.
But...  We can't do anything but
we have to try games
[Music]
so you need a ship to go on the
ocean of the sun Campbell are layers very
difficult if you need a ship to go on
that ocean of emptiness so the
book made in layers is called Lucian on
Vanity and then Choni Lama wrote
a book a ship that you can use on
the ocean of emptiness and it's like a
joke he's talking about the leader are layers
I'm going to be your ship's captain I
have a good ship in this ship
we can cross are layers without problems
so let's finish the commentary
in fact Choni Lama he also writes the
second commentary called Pulling on the
Difficult Points in Wisdom also
we're going to use this the greatest commentary
of all time on the
hen is Chandra Kirti
around 650 AD he wrote
a book called Entering the Middle Way
he wrote the commentaries Entering the
Middle Way also called Kabbalah that it is
and the other one is called Plaza Navarra
and I'm called Clarifying the Words
the Plaza Navarra commentary explains the
words of wisdom this book that you
are studying and Entering the
Middle Way explains the  meaning and these
books are the basis of all the
teachings of emptiness with physics
from the countries you come from: Vietnam,
China, Korea
[Music]
box client
The books arrived, said the
Tang Dynasty, left by Jan Steen, and the
messages
were translated by the other group of nut mixtures. They
spread it yesterday, Korea before, and then
the Japanese took it from the companies
of the tan industry, and they are still there in
Japan, very strong.
That's how this book came. What is the
name of the book of wisdom? It's just
called wisdom.
People have these long names. What
is the Sanskrit, Brasilia?
The Russians have the correct
pronunciation. The correct pronunciation is nana. The
Russian pronunciation of these words
is very pure, very close. Justin doesn't
mean knowing, practice means
super knowledge, wisdom. Same, Xcode,
and the Garena book is just called
wisdom. Since we are studying, if
the first homework question says
what is the ship on the ocean of
emptiness? The ocean of emptiness is the
decision-making comment, layer, and it needs.
We need a ship to continue
benefiting, and it is the comment, in fact,
not even the most.
And we are going to give you a
notebook, and all the  Days we're going to
give you more things to put in that
notebook.
There's a 55-page one on the Lion's Spear. We're still
improving the Mets.
Chi Chi is based on the teachings of
Maitreya called
The Sight,
The Ornament of Realization.
[Music]
James is
not,
and very famous lines.
5 It's like Singapore comes from there,
Singapore coming and lion,
the city of lions.
You from Singapore are the median,
so that's the ocean about the
emptiness of a ship on the ocean of
emptiness. How many courses are we going to have
about Narim? 5. Try to come to
everyone. Yes, I have to repeat or I have to
remember.
It's difficult for me to teach 50
people and then I have to go back and
teach another 50 people. I have to
waste time repeating.
So if you don't build, if you don't
build the paths, you're going to go off
the paths. Influence three years.
In the first course, we study the two
chapters. How many chapters are there in
Wisdom? 27. Very famous,
27 chapters. And we study the names of
the chapters and the structure of the
chapters,
and like a hen  He chose to teach
emptiness. His nickname is the area.
Those from New York call themselves
New York City,
and the people from Mexico City
call Mexico City. It's
like if the people from Huancayo call Wang
Ya China. So, the area
and the greater area are denying that it exists. So
sometimes we just call it the
sensitive area. The people from Mexico City,
the view from Mexico, what Mexico City,
what?
So we finished the first two
chapters. So I had a great new
age yesterday. The one before
wanted to learn some Sanskrit
while we learn wisdom. So
you should learn some
important words. So for each assignment, I'm
going to give you three. I'm going to give you three
Sanskrit words.
So that's going to be almost enough
for you to speak for Sainz when you go
to Segovia.
And the Indonesian language is
very similar, he explained. We're going to learn some
Sanskrit words while we go.
You should learn some. If
we're going to learn three
Sanskrit words each class of Gambari,
there are two things in  Your homework is okay.
By the way, I put the words in your homework,
and they have the meanings of the words
and the roots of the words that
came into English.
That's called
cognates. It means that the word came
from Sanskrit almost directly into
English.
It's very important to know the cognates.
What is the combination of press, psni,
action? I
know that's why
English has static,
irritable.
The reason why English has a
street, I know, comes from signs. It's the
Sanskrit j that came from the k, and that's why it's
this weird spelling in English, which is the
street. I know, it's to make them, even so they don't know
these cognates. Can you remember the
Sanskrit?
[Music] I
told you yesterday what's important.
Blood is in everything. The Buddhas speak
Sanskrit. Pixels,
all the modesty speaks Sanskrit.
When you become a base, you have to
speak Sanskrit, so you should
start now.
Second, you can express yourself to your friends.
You can impress your friends, and these
are a cocktail party. Do you know why there's a
k in English? I can tell you.
Each chapter is called a grill.
This number, so that's in.  Your homework:
one of the three Sanskrit words.
Quiz: the bulls in your homework with
the explanation and the meaning, and
that the cooking you have to memorize. You have to
memorize those three, and one
of them is enough on YouTube. The fifth
exam if you want to know which one to win
ten dollars.
Maybe Paris
Alexia means to examine and analyze the
question. I like the word
investigation. Each chapter is of
wisdom. It's an investigation. We are
checking something. We are checking a
question. Action, and that is the structure
of our production. And that is the
structure that is a homework question. It's a
Paris. Each chapter is called
Paris
Investigation.
We are checking like the police investigation.
Winston. The structure of wisdom. Each
chapter is a journalist means
investigate. It's an investigation. The
structure of each chapter is the same
as, okay, this homework. The first thing is,
wind stupid. Someone is going to come up with a
dumb idea.
As my husband told me, he is
yelling at me in the kitchen because he is
tired. He hasn't eaten and there was a lot of
traffic.
[Music] Okay,
Buddhism. That is super stupid.
An idea of ​​superiority because he
is studying you. Because
your husband is yelling at you tonight. Yes, because he is
tired.  I didn't make dinner and he had a lot of
traffic
[Music]
If you're going to write a chapter, if you're going to
write chapter 28 of Wisdom,
and you can call it The Husband in the
Kitchens, and the first sentence would be,
someone's going to come to that structure,
someone's going to come and give a
distant life because your husband wrote to you
because he's tired and doesn't do anything, and your
husband and his boss at work yelled at him,
and there was a lot of traffic, so it's going to come
to someone, it was going to be a stupid idea, and
then Nagarjuna is going to refute the
story.
His style,
I want to see that in your homework, his style is
simple, it's simple, simple
and elegant, his style is simplicity,
elegance and practicality. He always uses
short words, well, he shortens,
and he uses the ideas of the normal world,
and they are the ideas of the normal world, like in
your homework, the light, the last homework in your
homework is called Gray, it's called True
Application, a true application
[Music].
Lagarde was very good at that, he was the
greatest philosopher in ancient India,
and what made him great is that he
took it to the kitchen, and he almost always
takes it to the kitchen. He doesn't just do blah blah
blah of philosophy, he always  It takes you to the
kitchen, so your homework every day is a
real app, and you have to make
a real app. If you don't know how to
do it, ask at home. He can
teach you the party pills, and
maybe Tim will organize the computing for
the real app. You know, James, it's the
gaming course.
These are the gas courses since they're
learning at night. So
people started talking to me about courses, they
started demanding business relationship courses.
So you, the gay course,
to see how they know it in the
business, in the kitchen. Then he says, "Oh, that's
the real delight of
boys." He says, "Oh, that's the gay course. It's
for families that are fighting and
for people who want a business
because they pay me so much money to give them the
money, to deliver the money. It's
because I know how to make a real app,
and I know how to do it, and if you have to do it, he
says, 'I
'm going to be here for three years
every day,
and people are giving and giving money. I
'm like, so I want to teach you. Take
the law if there is one, and do it,' he tells me, 'there, and
that's called a real app.' The
best example is, teach, China has been
the most incredible city in  The difference in the
world now is that this
Chinese soft power program is
very similar to
today, so I went, I have to go
directly from that man to you,
these are executives, executives from China,
we have a group here, thank you for
coming. Just like now,
the first time I had the software, I was
n't ready, I was very busy, I had to be,
give me a mouse, be in, exercising
the manual, I was telling them, and I had an
860-page manual to design, my
head was exploding, my last hair was
falling out, John Brady knows, number
one, your hair falls out and then your
ears fall out, I don't know why, so
I'm stressed, I'm not prepared for
Chinese soft power, and it was thought that it would be an
idea that I said, Stanley and Alison, let's have
the students do the course,
and that will be the course, so we told them
that they have to take the material
and they have to do a real application,
so they arrived, ready, the translation
of Jackson, we are translating one of the
biggest books of the church, so
what are they going to do, eight thousand pages of
translation, so they arrive well to the
translation class and they have to
do  their own applications, and that's
the idea,
and you're going to invent the next
husband in the kitchen.
It's an exercise for you, the
first ones who go, the first ones who,
after five years, are going to look at you
and be
totally stupid and bad, but they're going to
learn how
Juan Jasso did something good. It's being very good, it
was incredible. So
talk about it if you don't know.
So you have to, for each task, you have to
take these ideas and how to use them in your
real life. People are going to ask
why you came to Arizona.
I learned some business strategies
from 2,200,000 years ago. I wasn't just
sitting in the desert. I'm going to
get rich, okay?
[Music]
Who did that before? What's the name of the
chicken? And he made real applications, and
his style was, let a person come
and say a dumb idea.
Paris, to each pair, that's
research. The stupid one comes along, and
Nagarjuna
beats him with real,
true applications. And then he comes along, and he
said, "Not even the best." There, this didn't
Nagarjuna do it, it comes from an
old plate. It identifies each pair, and if someone
comes  And it says something silly, my husband
is yelling at me because he was tired and
because you're really liking it because he even
yells at your children
last week. The first one is a very stupid one and
then there's a real application and then
the real scripture follows.
They say, by the way, Tandil, don't think that
Nagarjuna did this. This comes
directly from the suffering heart in the
structuring and the ma is going to say, or
look, this comes from the Buddha. There isn't
one, he's just quoting the Buddha.
Stop talking so much about Shola and
we finish the first two chapters. In
the first chapter it was an examination
of conditions, factors,
how one thing makes another thing
happen. That's the first chapter.
The second chapter, for ten dollars,
your face,
mister, to several, Mr. Greedy,
shopping, ten dollars.
And the second chapter, how you arrive, how you
leave, what happens when you arrive, what happens when you leave, when I
enter through the door, I see through
the door, what are you really
happening to?
Images come out of my mind, small, strong, bigger, bigger,
bigger,
and then I go out through the door, smaller, smaller, smaller. I do
n't walk, I don't go through the door,
images, images. Then we call it
walking, gay, the anus walks through the door
of Xela, I never walk through  no door
picture small door big door big door big door small door small door small
door we
call it walking nagarjuna would say it's not
real
he would never say that more real that is real it
's a real walk
the way
the way you thought how you got out through that
door that's more real how you got there
Damon a lot of one answer nagarjuna
and
you gave wright to other people in
the past that's all it doesn't get
here in a car doesn't get here on a
highway didn't you fly forget that you had
helped others get somewhere else
Magaly one says that's real that's
real flying in an airplane that's not real
that's not what happens that's like the
husband who is angry because in the
beginning it's not real ok
that's the second chapter now we go to the
third chapter we are going to study six
chapters this time
three of them are short chapter
three chapter four and chapter five are
short how many did I say 6
yes we are going to study 6 6 3 4 5 6 7 and 8 so
in your homework the question more
homework that is not on your exam so don't
Study, it's very long for an
exam
[Music] They
fear the names of the Pharisees, what
are the names of the chapters, and if
by the way the deadlines of the countries to
be a father,
ixe
Paris means around
when you want to find a cooked in
English in a way and it's very
easy to change them for it's
speaking generally the one in Sanskrit
changes one in English what does it mean to
you they
say in English barry like periscope or
perimeter
means around like a periscope
cndh the submarine that you can see
around perimeter means the edge
around something but it only means
around
dexia means to see
and that came
[Music]
to German which is which is the root of
English like something and that became
ocular
and words for the eye
popular optometrist
these words
and many words of red eye comes from
Africa
eye comes from ixe
so Paris means to check it all
around they examine investigate
investigate who is being
investigated for 20 dollars
Guardiola initiation
for 20 dollars
and who is being investigated
[Music]
in this book who is being
investigated
you have  I've been
young
while you
ESPN investigates
and more
[Music]
who's being investigated
he's the investigator I
'm canceled the money
we can spend all day
he's investigating these other
stupid guys my husband is upset he
yells at me all day and maybe he's
hungry you bad day
let's investigate that and let's
investigate what you said okay he's the
first guy that comes in every episode
they're being investigated why
did you say that thing is so stupid we have to
check we have to check we have to check
why is he  s bad I am
[Music]
so each chapter is called a paris
when I made it together when I made it
together with the and it becomes a long and but I
made it simple in its task so it
really is padilla because it is barí and
the doses come together and it becomes
longer for you
[Music]
means I'm going to check I'm going to investigate
sánchez and chapters 3 investigation of
the powers of the powers in sense
the powers of the senses
[Music]
and power of sense we're going to check the
ears the ears and the mind the
hearing the taste the eyes ears nose mouth
body mind we're going to
investigate the senses
the power of the senses and say would
emit interest means power power
the sense
so they only have three words in
Sanskrit it is
said while
in the ancient books of Asia indra is
a means power there was a god
while means a very powerful one in
English I won
comes from indra free to mean
don andrés means the super powerful
means that your eye is powerful your
nose is powerful your tongue has the
power and here we're going to play the text of
Sudan
5  Link the Wheel of
Life to your team to experience the
world. Without this team, you can't touch
things, you can't do things well. So let's
check where these powers came from.
Indra, ah,
what's the cooking? I won, I won. There's no
Indra,
the Hindu god, powerful god. And let's
investigate the powers. This comes in
your homework. All good. In total, in what you
ate, good in your homework.
[Music]
2.
And he could say goodbye. Hundreds and hundreds of
readings. And that's divided into three turns
of the wheel. The first period of your life
is called
the boring period.
[Music] There are
5 additions. There are 12. There are 18 categories. There are
the four noble truths. There are the
six perfections of the body. You know, like a
lot of lists, it's like a counter. This
is the counter period. Just make
long lists. And all the people from the
first period, Granderson, what's
number 6? 17. No, it's not number 17.
That's called vilar more. Also, up to
here,
and you give a translation of helping
nerds. That was the  Buddha's first teaching
in the second period of his life,
Buddha said to the people, "You're just making
lists. I'm going to teach you emptiness."
Singh Sensing, the result of the
diamond cutter, is okay. In the second
period of his experiences, what happened in
the third period? You have the nerds. They
met the emptiness people and
had a disagreement. So I could say,
after the second period, "How do you
like it, those who teach?" The
nerds said, "We like everything. Everything
is a list." The emptiness people said, "No, no,
no." He only taught emptiness for
ten more years.
Everything is emptiness, forget the list.
Then they had a big fight. Then they
got to just, like people say, "Oh, oh, yeah,
there we go, let's ask Gisela. We have to
make the list. Congressional, as she is
going to tell us which one is correct." They
wasted time, gas, gas at the
base of referrals.
If any, and soloists, they will be taken care of, they
go together.
[Music]
That's called the third turning of the wheel,
and there came the school, only that they
go together. I
cooperated. Don't make me a referee,
you two,
because I'm talking about that.
Chapter number  Chapter
4 and chapter 5 are for the
nerds. Chapter 3, chapter 4, and
chapter 5 are for the likes. It's for
people who like views and
old jokes. 5 added: 12 gates
of the senses, 18 categories, 4
supreme truths, 4 ways of being born, 2 the
bond, 12 bonds of dependent origination.
Chapter 3, chapter 4, chapter 5: those
nerds, the nerds of life, who
took control of Buddhism for 700 years.
The nerds were the great Buddhists
for 700 years after the
Buddha died. What happened? The emptiness ones
were probably meditating Buddhists.
Then two Merckx took over for
700 years.
[Music]
Everyone loved Christmas for 700 years.
Buddhism became a religion of
nerds, and they translated it into a stick figure and a lot of
black stuff.
Honestly, it's dry. It's drier than seeing
very badly. I translated it for two years. I
already memorized a lot of this.  If not
exactly
mind
[Music]
and so I respect it but it's boring
in chapter 3, chapter 4 and
chapter 5 the nerds come and we have to
make them see Paris art,
we have to investigate them, they're going to come and
say stupid things, it's like a
police investigation, you think here's
chapter 3, Buddha, the Lord, the
senses, the
power of the senses,
how do you know you have these contacts
between keys,
in the case of the eye, between the contact
between the color blue
[Music],
the eye that detects and then the mind that
interprets the color blue. In Buddhism
these are called the powers, sometimes
divided into 12 and 6 senses, 6 objects,
visible things, audible things, things that can be smelled, things that can be
tasted, things that can be
felt, things
that can be thought, and the 6 consciousnesses
about whether the things... these are from
the fundamental teachings, in the
first turning of the wheels, the gates of
the senses, I already sensed
that they think the nerd comes and says
100 dollars, already
10 9 8 7 6  5 4 3 2
what was my question
says that the senses come from oneself
he says
and puppets are real your eye are you
seeing me miner chicken can you see me you have
an eye it works it works on its
own side don't tell me these things about
emptiness
buddha taught it wood taught the powers
of the sense 20 that the first the first
turning of the wheel of dharma is that those
things put on it emptiness is coming what are you
telling me about the eye not
being real the truth I'll take out your eye you'll still
see things if I take out your
eye are upset
[Music]
says the eye really sees things you
need the eye the eye works don't
tell me it's empty don't tell me it doesn't
work what are you talking about are you
seeing me nagarjuna how are you
seeing me a are you using your eye ah but it
's not real everything is empty if you know so you ca
n't see me are very angry with
the chicken
you are the one from the second turning of the wheel of
dharma because buddha spent so much time
during the first turning of the wheel
teaching the six senses that's how
we communicate with him  The world isn't
empty, it's not my real, it's super
real. You can't even
hear my
stupid comments if you don't use your
ears, which have their own power. Why do you
call it power? They have
their own power. They're not empty.
That's how you communicate with the world.
That's chapter 3. We're going to talk more.
We're going to talk more.
I'm good. You want to line up
and you're going to have a chapter from chapter 1 to 3
and then another from chapter 4 and you're going to go home and
meditate. I want you to feel the bridges
between the chapters, so each assignment,
each class is mainly based on one
chapter, then a taste of the
next chapter. Chapter number 4,
chapter number 4: research the parts
of a person.
Hits 5 aggregates. In English, you
can call it body and hand. You can
call it the five aggregates because they're
called five degrees. They're the five parts
of a person. They're called the five
aggregates. And why for 20 dollars?
It's a cheap question.
Stanley, where are you? Why are they called
aggregates?
[Music]
Because they help, or did they say parts of a
person? They're just five parts of a
person.
Learn with Hits, Picas, and Hard to Them All
Together
Network.
[Music]
Life says
we call  Aggregates because they are clusters of a
lot of things. Many have many things
piled up, that's why they are called
aggregates or clusters.
Just think that people are
made of five groups of things: your
body, your thoughts, feelings, your
discriminations, your mind, and everything
else. Also, you have your body, many
parts, and in these feelings, many
feelings,
in this discrimination about things, this is
good, this is bad, many types of
discriminations, you have many types of
consciousness. It's
not the bad finger, it's the third finger.
And you have everything else, everything else they
have. So in chapter 4 we are going to
investigate the five parts, the five
aggregates of people, and
especially we are going to see, we are going to
study the first aggregate.
The first one is your body because
the stupid man of the first
turn of the wheel arrives. In the first three
chapters, it is the counters that arrive. There are
55 aggregates. Which is the first
aggregate? The physical body. The
physical body. You're telling me that the
physical body is not real. You want me to tell you why it
is empty? You have to hit me with
my hand. It is not real, a state of
emptiness. It does
n't have, they
say, this super real. You feed it
every day, a lot of food, no means.
What is emptiness? That's chapter 4.
We're in Paris. There are two parts to a
person, but we're focusing on the body.
In the first part,
in chapter 5
[Music].
According to Buddhism and
quantum physics, the physical body is
made of different energies:
gravitational energy, electronic force
[Music].
Protons, electrons, neutrons—
what is it?
And there are other things, chemical elements,
molecules. Science and Buddhism
both say that there are chemical elements
in the body: elemental
gravitational forces, electrical force.
These create the physical body.
So Buddha taught his elements.
Sometimes they're called the 18, sometimes they're
called the 5. Sachs
Lung never
[Music].
Earth, water, fire, wind, and space—
these are the five elements in
Buddhism. Singh,
don't think they're some stupid thing. To
people who know about
cell phones, this is
gravitational force. The legibility is very
sophisticated. Do
n't you think the ancient Buddhist people
were stupid? And style,
they have 60 levels of electrons.
The sizes are written in life,
armed two light-years. I do
n't think the five are stupid.
Elements aren't some kind of medieval science
where they make people bleed. They're the ones who are
most excessive. They're very sophisticated
about the body's energy sources,
so they go from the body to the
elements to the chemicals in the body,
how it works. Which is the sexiest of the
five:
earth, fire, water,
wind, and space? Which
is the sexiest? It has to be space.
So the chicken focuses on the
sexiest one, the last one, space. Five
aggregates. Let's talk about the first one, the physical one,
the body. In the last chapter, in this
chapter, five chemicals that make up your
body, five elements, forces. We have to
talk about the last one, joke, because it's
more interesting. Space, that
space.
What does it mean to say that space is
empty? Which chapter are we going to? Chapter 1. Which
chapter are we going to? 5, 6, 6?
3 was about the powers. 4 was about
the aggregates. 5 is about the
elements. Now we come to chapter 6.
We're going to investigate attachment and desire. Desire
and attachment.
The counters are almost going out
the door. The chicken, by the way,
chapters 3, 4, and 5 are short because the
chicken is bored with the counters.
Stupid, stupid, stupid. We can, if
something more interesting comes along, like the
Desire that keeps you in this world that
your body created. Let's talk
about desire, the emptiness of desire, and the
extinguishing of attachment.
Here I'm going to give you a key to
manifesting from chattering,
and I heard the name of the chapter.
I was there when I wanted everything. He
ate his first donuts,
so he says, "
How is he the son of [uncle Miguel]?" and he's never
eaten anything interesting since.
Green measures. We're chatting for [unclear].
And if the waiter brought a lot of [unclear]
churros,
he says, "Activate, try this, isn't it?"
And he was like, more
that desire
[Music].
And then came a second one of "I want, I want," it's
like, I resigned,
then it became attachment. First
desires
thanks to what he had tasted. It was his Uncle
Miguel who gave them, and then he started
crying because he couldn't take it, because he couldn't
get it. That's desire and
attachment, but it's not. This isn't the
chapter, it's not about this. It smells like that,
but it's wrong. I'm going to
teach you the right one after we
investigate
what desire and detachment are. So
remember, I'm going to [unclear].  Tell them when I
get to chapter 7, it's very long, it's
the second longest chapter, the
longest chapter is the one
after it, and it's the one about the four truths,
not by much, but it's longer. This
chapter 7 is a super chapter, you have to
investigate
how things begin, how they stay,
and how they stop, how things
start, how things stay, and how
things stop. Life has
weapons, they never teach you in that order for
300 dollars,
and guess how, and they don't get
partial credit, guess how, teaching about
life, weapons, and why.
Oh
[Music]
The setting in life, they always teach
without expressing
stop and stay, they never say start, stay, stop, start, stop,
and
stay without listening, and they start, they stop,
why? Because I'm going to teach
if it doesn't want you to
stay attached to it, it
stays, what, the one that
you stay is like this, you're going to be born and
how you're going to die
in pieces, it stops and stays because
staying is very short, it's not worth
talking about. You have
chapter 7, and chapter 7 is going to talk a
lot about
the starting, they're at the beginning of
starting
From singing in the Senate, it's
not just about starting, it's not just about
staying and stopping. Starting has to
begin, it has its own beginning. They have their
staying, and for him, it has
their stopping. They
want the beginning of the beginning, they're going to
start, for the beginning to
stay.
This is a weapon. People say the
beginning of the beginning has a beginning, the beginning of the beginning of the beginning of the beginning
has a beginning. So he says,
no, don't ask me. They got tired
after a while. So the hen
says, where is the beginning of the beginning of the
beginning of school? Because chapter
number 8, they're going to investigate
who does things and what
agents and actions do,
and what they do
if things are empty. How
can people do things if things
are empty? How can you have
breakfast?
I'm thinking beyond the
yoga class to the important things. We did it
at Tussam, member of Bryant
1.
We had a small class with
a big lunch.
[Music]
How we start things, and we're going to talk
specifically about how you make a vase.
How does someone who makes vases make
a vase? Because until they make a
vase, you can't call them one.  that makes
vases
like the potter makes vases you ca
n't call the one who makes a jar
the one who makes vases that makes a vase
because he doesn't make vases until
a vase is born
good
in the study of emptiness and the
specialty of the hen and her
specialty is when her mate starts
something is wrong something is completely
more with those images of her style
a husband is upset because he
yelled at me and I was hungry and the hen says
something bothers me about Sophie something doesn't
seem right about that that's
her style
[Music]
when they say the cook made the
food that bothers me you can't say
the cook made the food the
cook didn't make the food until he
made the food because cooks
make food like that until you don't have the
food how can you have a sentence that
starts with the cook
before I hear the word food
because the cook isn't a cook
until there's a food and that bothers me
is the style of the throat every couple
so we say something and she says it does
n't bother me
the whole world is weird everything seems wrong
something else is happening you feed me
your husband gives him enough
sleep there's no traffic and you  It
keeps bothering me, or something is bothering me. There's
something else going on. It
must be a rap song. Something else
is happening. He's not the traffic,
plus dinner. Anyway, he yelled at me. There's
something else going on. You're bothering me.
That's the chicken's style. And this
thing about losses, people
doing things, bothering me. It's the root of
grilling. First, you have to get annoyed,
and then you have to check what's
really going on. And it comes up. It's
like,
and you're going to come to the conclusion that
yelling at kids is his style. They've
finished the introduction to the
first six chapters that we're going to
study these ten days. We're going to
review these ten chapters. They're
good, homies. We have a
peanut for... I mean, like
Gisela. I hope, I hope so. I
have 15 minutes, right? And I'm going to ask
what common theme connects the first
three chapters. They're
all the themes that Buddha taught
in the beginning. They're basic courses. We had
60 classes in Sedona in 10 or 12 days.
Many of the books that we're
translating, the one from Sudan, we also have to
go to Stan's book.  Read
Stanley's boring book for
basic information. Everyone complains about
Stanley's book. Everyone wants to translate the
book, and Xavi because it's sexy and has
tandran. He's the only book that has
cakes,
and everyone is bored with
Stanley Pando's book. Stanley
Pando,
but we all have to go to his book.
Many of the translators are stealing
parts from his book for their own books
because this is basic Buddhism,
fundamental Buddhism. The accountants were right. You do
n't need
[Music]
this fundamental Buddhism.
You have to know the five
accumulators. You have to use the 18
categories. You have to be the 12
vehicles of interdependence. You must
know the four truths.
Basic fundamental Buddhism
because it is significant that these three
chapters 3, 4, and 5, basic Buddhism,
what happened after 700, 22 years that
the accountants took over,
what happened, the chicken happened,
and you have to feel this, what happened to
those accountants, who ran the
accountants from Buddhism, Nagarjuna. He said,
we have to make it something sexier,
and we're going to give them  Emptiness, emptiness,
emptiness, they're like, really, so
after 700 years he arrived
[Music]
and changed Buddhism forever.
What you know is you know 700 years of
just monks, and the monks were bored,
Solomon, and repeating lists,
and after doing time, seen on the
streets, nobody will be more intense, and without that
comes
the inventor of the wheel and the Steve
Jobs of the hustle and bustle. He made it tremble
[Music]
He told us, he didn't say, 'You have to be it in a certain
way,' he said, 'Let's go to true
Buddhism, emptiness, emptiness, emptiness, and
body cheetah love.
You accountants, are you aware that
the world is on fire? Are you aware
that everyone is going to fall and die? Are you
aware that there are 600,000
people dying of hunger, of wars,
because you're making lists?
Do something that will help
people, creatures, the dollar. A
chicken woke you up so that in this
accounting, let's return to love
[Music]
Silks, yes, no,
your quantity, and yes, you will be rich,
and if you follow your morality, you will always
be happy
[Music]
If you are patient you will be beautiful. If you have fun
at your job you will be a leader.
If you meditate your mind will be at peace,
Winston. If you learn about
wisdom you will be fun. But
[Music]
Love achieves them all. Focus on
love. Who said that, Nagar?
So significant that this
teaching is very significant that he is
teaching our remaining chapters. You
are witnessing the breaking of the
counters, the change in Buddhism from
Dayana and Mahajanga, the path to the great
path of love, compassion, caring for
others,
and using emptiness. Use emptiness to
save other people. In this book, in
these chapters, you are witnessing the
complete change,
the chapter change between
chapters 6 is emerging. You have to
be aware. It's
completely new music.
Low Fighter IV.
I would like to do a yoga class in Love
and I'm going to try.
And by the way,
Nick couldn't come because what
should be called mooncake came, but his
wife  He said I don't know that she was born during the
cake because she was born during the cake
mooncake her name is Amelie we went to
see the speed she is very beautiful she has
all her fingers and everything she is beautiful she is
super beautiful
if we are thinking that the bears
of Nick's genes didn't get there
with her she is super beautiful she
must be the mom
Nick's text is a chicken using
the Himma Jana to teach emptiness
to the gymnasts more
[Music]
using the sutras of the gymnasts to
teach Hitler Yang's
emptiness if it is very calm relaxed
our friend
the message in your life here
[Music]
because not all the classes we are going to
do in the second section talk about it
of its own nature
aspirins don't have anything inside
aspirins that can take away your
headache aspirins don't have
anything inside aspirins that
can take away your headache
nothing
is like thinking that the husband is
upset because no because there is no
scene there is nothing inside aspirin that
can take away your headache
what is the proof of this that it doesn't
always work don't get on a plane
if it doesn't work  Half the time you're going to
fall and die
[Music] You do
n't keep taking aspirin when it does
n't work half the time. Try
to see how it actually works
all the time. This is called emptiness, not
self-nature. Here's your third
word in Sanskrit: atman,
adman, an. What is self-nature?
What is
command?
[Music]
Describe a brand of atman aspirin.
It has a chemical inside that
works, which is called the
active ingredient. That's the atman. Atman means
if I have something inside that makes it
work. A nature comes from it.
Aspirin has something inside, a
self-nature, that makes it work.
That fake thing that doesn't work is called
atman. And in Sanskrit, in
Buddhist writing, pib for the person, for the
people ascribed to atman. It can be a
word for God.
Don't go with your industrial friends,
say hardman, maya, ways, command. It's
a bad aspirin. They're going to be respectful.
Respect the word atman in your religion.
The thing inside the aspirin
that makes it work, that doesn't work,
that doesn't exist. There's no chemical
inside aspirin that makes it
work.  And weeds are going to have to give
the roots of the word atman, say
shaman,
they call it meaning
we are in the zone of or because they don't believe
in God,
the US population is apathetic
against the crimes of certain people of the
religious meaning
[Music]
came to Greek as the initial
meaning to
live,
what is an atom, that which cannot be
divided, it has also touched me, three
or that which cannot be divided, that's why it is
called atom, atman is related to
time, the word temple, right now we are, for
example, it comes from the same root and so
because in ancient days the temple
was separate from the people, they didn't put it
in the middle of the temple because the people were
dirty,
the temple must be separate, it is more
from the people, temple a separate place
[Music]
one of my dreams is one of those, it is in
your
yellow homework, intrigue and partner,
you have two minutes, maybe
Wisin 2003 is
not subject to King Coin,
it's that you are
already this medium
hahaha
what
[Music]
part of the people
in the life of things, two types of the
city, people and things, where are the
voids in the kitchen, you
should  going back and forth
where are the bases where
it's just the waiting of the cow of the
people is the wife rather the husband
[Music]
the thing is the gray is very good 60
dollars
a day a 60 answer values ​​in the
50 question perfect answer
in Israel big head means
responsible linense and then it's
perfect in the kitchen the emptiness of the
person is the husband I didn't do anything
[Music]
that doesn't exist doesn't exist
there is proof that there is
proof that he is angry a
red tail a loud noise and it is
definitely proof of his face and
color of his face about the wrinkles
all these are real so
sometimes we can say that the
husband I didn't do anything nice that me
real but look that you see the red face the
sound and the wrinkles those are real the
parts are real the person wasn't me
the husband I didn't do anything doesn't work
but who says his red face I didn't do
his broken face and the icio his red face he
made it wrinkle he made the sounds
the hen says I'm going to Paris Charles or
something smells bad about it something  It's
wrong
[Music]
that's called the emptiness of things
red face wrinkles
those are new care of things that last a
lifetime the specific red face
in the kitchen who made the red face
and you have a red face when the
sight even of your children doesn't have the
pieces they exist you
and the whole you made the whole is
the husband the greasy ones on the
red face the loud sound now you know the
connection the whole structure of wisdom
is around your two types of
emptiness to take care of people and
things where we're going to be in
this entire session we're going to be in the
emptiness of
yes they
had 50% of the cancer
the body parts the senses of
power ok
mainly the last question no
[Music]
before almost in the discussion of the eye
six technical bites that goes to a couple and
they take the most important thing when
you teach the five aggregates you take your
body
[Music]
when you teach the five elements they
focus on space something sexy when
they take the powers
the life weapon says 90% of
human experience is visual
[Music] you
normally judge people by  It's not
how they smell, but how they look. It's
worn out with your eyes.
Now, if the eye is seeing things self-
existing on its own,
then it should always see everything.
If the sky is young, everything. If aspirin
cures, it should cure all the time.
When an aspirin doesn't work, sometimes there's
someone in the background saying, "That
bothers me. It has
the active ingredient. It really does
have the active ingredient. It doesn't work.
There's something that bothers me about its
purpose."
If aspirin has an active ingredient, something
inside that takes away your headache, it
should always work. If your eye
has a right to see, it should
always see.
When you see, you
should see $100
because your mind.
If there are suicides, and the eye should see
the eye.
If the eye has a right to see, so,
if the eye has seen inside what's there,
when you see the sky,
your eye should also know.
And if there's something, if there's something you don't see with
your eye, then the eye isn't like
aspirin.
If an aspirin doesn't work
40 percent of the time, 30 times,
then it doesn't work the way you
thought it would.
And if there's something the eye can't see
that's next to the eye, then the
eye...  It doesn't work the way you
thought, Sintys. The eye isn't seeing
things. It's just that
your eye isn't doing anything,
and you've helped people. You've helped
blind people. My mom
has macular degeneration. If you're
already helping
blind people,
spend a week helping them laugh, helping
blind people read, and their eyes
are improving. Do you understand why the eye
sees?
Because it helps others see things that
have nothing to do with chemicals and
the cornea.
And you see because you've given
vision to others because you've taken care of
someone else's eyes.
[Music]
I know I don't have any more time, but remember
where I'm going to take it from. [
Music]
One more homework question.
[Music]
The Sandman's Tale, Chicken Returns,
Chapter 3. The Taleman comes and says, "I'd
like to make a suggestion, and the eye
is like a fire."
[Music]
And fire only burns other things.
Fire doesn't burn fires. If fire
burned fire,
then fire would be gone because it's
fire. It would burn fire. Just because something
does something doesn't mean it does.  You must do it
yourself because if that were the
fire would burn fire and
disappear
like a chicken. They refute it, I'm not going to
tell you
[Music]
and I don't
want your homework answer to
talk about walking towards the door,
which is the example you use
[Music],
which is the example you use and use fire
contact in what walking to the door
[Music]
and that state of the homework, don't forget
your apps,
your destination,
why
yes
[Music]
and
[Music] yes yes [
Music]
and yes yes yes
and yes
[Music]
what